Guide to the Jack Underhill papers, 1963-1997
George Mason University. Libraries. Special Collections & Archives
- Series 2: Reports, 1967-1990; (10.5 boxes)
  - General Accounting Office Reports-New Community Development Program, 1975 (Box 12, Folder 8)
    92.1
  - Rockefellar Bank, 1976 (Box 13, Folder 1)
    482.2
  - Gananda Reports and Remissions to Market Analysts, 1976 (Box 13, Folder 2)
    109.13
  - Report on National Growth and Development, 1976 (Box 13, Folder 3)
    105.5
  - Market Study Riverton New Town, 1976 (Box 13, Folder 4)
    116.2
  - Roosevelt Island, 1976 (Box 13, Folder 5)
    88.1
  - Panel on Title VII New Communitie Program, 1976 (Box 13, Folder 6)
    482.13
  - Legislative Task Force, 1977 (Box 13, Folder 7)
    482.11
  - New Communities Program Closeout Report, 1977 (Box 13, Folder 8)
    484.18
    - Booklet: U.S. Department of Housing and Urban Development, "New Communities Act of 1968", 1.
    - Paper: Anonymous, "New Communities: An Alternative to Unplanned Suburban Sprawl", no date; 2.
    - Press Release: Department of Housing and Urban Development, "History of the New Communities Program", January 18, 1978; 3.
    - Report: Jack A. Underhill, "Pro's and Con's of Abolition of Title VII", no date; 4.
    - Minutes: Department of Housing and Urban Development, "Minutes of New Communities Study Meeting", April 24, 1967; 5.
  - Appropriation Hearing Curzan Report, 1977 (Box 13, Folder 9)
    128.1
  - Title 8 1/2, 1977 (Box 13, Folder 10)
    80.2
  - Cedar Riverside Task Force Report, 1977 (Box 13, Folder 11)
    109.9
  - New-Towns-In-Town An Urban Policy Initiative Report, 1977 (Box 14, Folder 1)
    118.2
  - Jonathan-Survey Report, 1977 (Box 14, Folder 2)
    90.4
  - Jonathan-Survey, 1977 (Box 14, Folder 3)
    100.7
  - Legislation-New Initiatives, 1977-1978 (Box 14, Folder 4)
    482.8
  - New Town In Town Urban Policy New Town In Town Team Reports, 1978 (Box 14, Folder 5)
    122.3
  - Reportage Aerien Sur Les Villes Nouvelles de la Region D'Ile de France, 1978 (Box 14, Folder 6)
    98.3
  - New Town In Town (NTIT) Urban Policy New Town In Town Team Reports, 1978 (Box 14, Folder 7)
    122.2
  - Inspector General Reports on New Communities, 1978 (Box 14, Folder 8)
    94.3
  - Inspector General Reports on New Communities, 1978 (Box 14, Folder 9)
    94.4
  - Statistics, 1979 (Box 15, Folder 1)
    483.13
    - Table: Anonymous, "Projected Land Use in Title VII New Communities As Originally Planned (Acres and Percent)", no date; 1.
  - New Community Development Corporation Management Information Summary, 1979 (Box 15, Folder 2)
    99.2
  - Maumelle Report on Publicity, 1979 (Box 15, Folder 3)
    117.9
  - Suburbs and Rural New Towns, 1980 (Box 15, Folder 4)
    482.5
  - A Title VII Incentive for New Town in Town, 1980 (Box 15, Folder 5)
    482.4
  - Census Information-New Towns, 1980 (Box 15, Folder 6)
    144.5
  - Elk Grove Village-Census Reports, 1980 (Box 15, Folder 7)
    86.14
  - St. Charles-Census Reports, 1980 (Box 15, Folder 8)
    89.3
  - Woodlands-Kingwood Census Reports, 1980 (Box 15, Folder 9)
    89.2
  - Shenandoah-Census Reports, 1980 (Box 15, Folder 10)
    88.8
  - Park Forest South-Census Reports, 1980 (Box 15, Folder 11)
    88.4
  - Columbia, Maryland-Census Reports, 1980 (Box 16, Folder 1)
    86.13
  - Draft Final Maumelle Report Department of Housing and Urban Development Contract H-4257, 1980 (Box 16, Folder 2)
    103.3
  - Draft Final Maumelle Report Department of Housing and Urban Development Contract H-4257, 1980 (Box 16, Folder 3)
    103.4
  - Consultants-Section 5 drafts, 1980 (Box 16, Folder 4)
    125.5
  - Consultants-Section 5 drafts, 1980 (Box 16, Folder 5)
    125.6
  - Consultants-Section 5 drafts, 1980 (Box 16, Folder 6)
    125.3
  - Consultants-Section 5 drafts, 1980 (Box 16, Folder 7)
    125.4
  - Preliminary Report Community Assistance Study, 1981 (Box 16, Folder 8)
    99.9
  - Microfiche A-M, 1970s (Box 17)
  - Microfiche Mc-Z, 1970s (Box 18)
  - Planning New Towns: National Reports of the U.S. and U.S.S.R (2 copies), 1981 (Box 19, Folder 1)
    102.5
  - Appraisal Report-Park Forest South, 1981 (Box 19, Folder 2)
    99.5
  - Park Forest South-Supplement Environmental Impact Statement, 1981 (Box 19, Folder 3)
    99.6
  - Section 8H and Section 12, 1981 (Box 19, Folder 4)
    82.7
  - Section 12, 1981 (Box 19, Folder 5)
    82.08
  - Department of Housing and Urban Development a Department of Housing and Urban Development Handbook on Organization of Office of P.D. and R, 1981 (Box 19, Folder 6)
    81.6
  - Maumelle New Town Appraisal Report, 1981 (Box 19, Folder 7)
    116.7
  - The Legacy of New Communities-draft report, 1982 (Box 19, Folder 8)
    125.2
  - Lists of New Community Development Corporation's Central Files and LIsts of Files SEnt to Federal Records Center, 1982 (Box 19, Folder 9)
    138.5
  - Practicum, 1982 (Box 19, Folder 10)
    97.3
  - Certifications, 1982 (Box 19, Folder 11)
    81.1
  - Assignment Task Force, 1982 (Box 19, Folder 12)
    82.6
  - New Community Development Corporation Agenda OMB Hearings, 1982 (Box 20, Folder 1)
    99.3
  - New Community Development Corporation Agenda OMB Hearings, 1982 (Box 20, Folder 2)
    99.4
  - Section II 5, 1982 (Box 20, Folder 3)
    82.5
  - Summary-Dissolution of New Communities Development Corporation-Women T. Linguist Testimony before House Committee, 1983 (Box 20, Folder 4)
    82.9
  - Census Boundaries, 1980s (Box 20, Folder 5)
    127.7
  - Census material for New Communities Analyses List, 1980s (Box 20, Folder 6)
    144.4
  - Legislation Land Reserve and New Communities, 1990 (Box 20, Folder 7)
    127.5
- Series 3: Plans, 1969-1992; (5.5 boxes)
  The information in this series covers instructions for projects involved in different planned communities that the Underhill papers covers. The series has 65 folders in 5 boxes.
  - Fort Lincoln New Town Urban Renewal Plan, 1969 (Box 20, Folder 8)
    99.1
  - Proposed Legislation, 1969-1970 (Box 20, Folder 9)
    483.1
  - Planned-Unit Development, 1970 (Box 20, Folder 10)
    100.8
  - Park Central, 1971 (Box 20, Folder 11)
    483.11
    - Letter: Samuel Pierce to John Tower, October 18, 1983; 1.
    - Note: Grant E. Mitchell to Marica Dodge, April 4, 1986; 2.
    - Paper: Anonymous, "Relationship to HUD Goals", January, 1978; 3.
    - Table: Janet Kindall, "HUD Projects in Park Central, Port Arthur", ca. 1985; 4.
  - Project Proposals Information, 1971 (Box 21, Folder 1)
    129.3
  - Flower Mound New Town-Project Agreement, 1971 (Box 21, Folder 2)
    116.6
  - Legislation-Community Development Bank, 1971-1974 (Box 21, Folder 3)
    483.3
    - Committee Hearing: Subcommittee on Housing and Community Development, "Statement of Warren T. Lindquist, Personal Assistant to David Rockefeller for Development and Public Affairs", September 23, 29, 30, 1975; 1.
  - Legislation-Community Development Bank, 1971-1974 (Box 21, Folder 4)
    483.4
  - League of New Community Developers, 1972-1974 (Box 21, Folder 5)
    106.10
  - League of New Community Developers, 1972-1974 (Box 21, Folder 6)
    106.11
  - League of New Community Developers, 1972-1974 (Box 21, Folder 7)
    106.9
  - New Town In Town Papers-By Others, 1972 (Box 21, Folder 8)
    92.4
  - Title VII Changes (Legislation), 1973 (Box 22, Folder 1)
    482.16a
  - Title VII Changes (Legislation), 1973 (Box 22, Folder 2)
    482.16b
  - New Communities Program: Prospects and Opportunities Report, 1973 (Box 22, Folder 3)
    103.6
  - Government of New Towns, 1973 (Box 22, Folder 4)
    95.2
    - Options for New Service Delivery Systems in Reston, ca. 1976; 3.
    - Alternatives for Delivering Services in New Communities (Draft), ca. 1976; 4.
    - Institutional Innovation in New Towns: The Dual Developer Concept, ca. 1976; 5.
  - Section 4 Chapter I Project Lists, 1973 (Box 22, Folder 5)
    91.5
  - Community Planning for the Elderly, 1973 (Box 22, Folder 6)
    100.5
  - St. Charles, 1974 (Box 22, Folder 7)
    88.2
  - Project Agreement for Roosevelt Island New Community, 1974 (Box 22, Folder 8)
    105.12
  - Project Selection, 1974 (Box 22, Folder 9)
    129.4
  - Legislative Proposals, 1974-1975 (Box 22, Folder 10)
    482.15
  - Summaries of Major Evaluations of New Communities Program, 1975 (Box 22, Folder 11)
    98.4
  - Summaries of Major Evaluations of New Communities Program, 1975 (Box 22, Folder 12)
    98.5
  - Maumelle Mast Plan Update, 1975 (Box 23, Folder 1)
    117.8
  - Harbison, 1975 (Box 23, Folder 2)
    87.2
  - British New Towns IC, 1975 (Box 23, Folder 3)
    82.16
  - National Community Development Bank, 1976 (Box 23, Folder 4)
    482.14
  - Termination: Agreement, 1976 (Box 23, Folder 5)
    483.16
  - Federal Role In New Communities on Analysis of Program Options, 1976 (Box 23, Folder 6)
    98.9
  - Apportionment/Reapportionment (Market Analysis III 6b), 1976 (Box 23, Folder 7)
    86.1
  - Northeast Corridor Project, 1976 (Box 23, Folder 8)
    81.9
  - Business Plan II 8c-Department of Housing and Urban Development, 1976 (Box 23, Folder 9)
    82.12
  - Program Initiative, 1976 (Box 23, Folder 10)
    96.4
  - New Communities Administration-Original Business Plan, 1976 (Box 23, Folder 11)
    117.10
  - New Communities Administration-Original Business Plan, 1976 (Box 23, Folder 12)
    117.11
  - New Communities Administration-Original Business Plan, 1976 (Box 24, Folder 1)
    118.1
  - New Communities: Problems and Potentials Appendix C, 1976 (Box 24, Folder 2)
    116.5
  - New Community Development Corporation Business Plan for Transaction Quarter and Fiscal Year, 1977 (Box 24, Folder 3)
    104.4
  - New Community Development Corporation Business Plan for Transaction Quarter and Fiscal Year, 1977 (Box 24, Folder 4)
    104.5
  - New Directions, 1977 (Box 24, Folder 5)
    96.5
  - New Town In Town-Research and Background, 1977 (Box 24, Folder 6)
    92.3
  - Comprehensive Community Planning for Energy Management and Conservation Vol. 2 Draft Report, 1977 (Box 24, Folder 7)
    100.3
  - Internal New Towns Association [no. 2], 1977 (Box 24, Folder 8)
    95.4
  - Department of Housing and Urban Development Developers, 1977 (Box 24, Folder 9)
    91.7
  - Comprehensive Community Planning for Energy Management and Conservation Vol. II Final Report, 1977 (Box 25, Folder 1)
    100.4
  - Comprehensive Community Planning for Energy Management and Conservation Vol. I Final Report, 1977 (Box 25, Folder 2)
    100.2
  - Park Central, 1977-1981 (Box 25, Folder 3)
    483.10
    - Memo: William J. White to John Clinton and Jim Breagy, "Park Central", April 28, 1978; 1.
    - Paper: Trudy Fish, "Park Central", February 1981; 2.
    - Plan: New Community Development Corporation, "Park Central Development Plan", no date; 3.
  - "FY 1978 Business Plan" (Box 25, Folder 4)
    122.1
  - New Towns-In Town, 1978 (Box 25, Folder 5)
    92.5
  - Newfields New Community Project Draft Review, 1978 (Box 25, Folder 6)
    117.1
  - Housing, 1978 (Box 25, Folder 7)
    81.7
  - Draft Review of Newfields New Community Project-Review, 1979 (Box 25, Folder 8)
    130.8
  - Irvine, California Housing, 1979 (Box 25, Folder 9)
    90.3
  - List New Communities and Reading List, 1980 (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Department of Housing and Urban Development Developers, 1980 (Box 25, Folder 11)
    91.8
  - New Communities Program Review, 1980 (Box 26, Folder 1)
    103.2
  - Project Assignments and Summary of New Towns, 1980 (Box 26, Folder 2)
    102.3
  - Redirecting of Title VII New Communities Program Paper, 1980 (Box 26, Folder 3)
    118.3
  - Flower Mound-Summary, 1981 (Box 26, Folder 4)
    86.15
  - Title X, 1981 (Box 26, Folder 5)
    483.17
    - Memo: Jack A. Underhill to John B. Clinton, "Title X and Title VII", April 17, 1981; 1.
    - Letter: Jack A. Underhill to John B. Clinton, "Title X and Title VII", April 29, 1981; 2.
    - Memo: Lauren B. Sevins to Directors, Offices of Regional Housing, and Field Office Managers and Supervisors, "Title X Development Program", January 9, 1980; 3.
  - Summary Data-New Communities (includes 5.5 disk), 1981 (Box 26, Folder 6)
    86.2
  - Private Developers-Project Summary, 1981 (Box 26, Folder 7)
    82.1
  - Park Central, 1981 (Box 26, Folder 8)
    88.5
  - Radisson, 1982 (Box 26, Folder 9)
    87.7
  - Woodlands-Data Base, 1982 (Box 26, Folder 10)
    86.12
  - St. Charles-Data Base, 1982 (Box 26, Folder 11)
    86.11
  - Harbison-Data Base, 1982 (Box 26, Folder 12)
    86.9
  - Shenandoah-Data Base, 1982 (Box 26, Folder 13)
    86.7
  - Jonathan-Data Base, 1982 (Box 26, Folder 14)
    86.10
  - Park Forest South-Data Base, 1982 (Box 26, Folder 15)
    86.6
  - Flower Mound-Data Base, 1982 (Box 26, Folder 16)
    86.8
  - Project List, 1983 (Box 26, Folder 17)
    82.3
  - New Town-Put, 1985 (Box 26, Folder 18)
    93.1
  - Program Information Summary, 1992 (Box 27, Folder 1)
    82.10
  - Roosevelt Island-Project Contract, 1990s (Box 27, Folder 2)
    91.2
- Series 4: Places, 1968-1985; (11.5 boxes)
  The documents in these folders include general information on different planned communities. These communities are in the United States and from foreign countries. The series also includes census data and computer printouts. The series has 91 folders in 12 boxes
  - Greenbelt Towns Revisited, 1968 (Box 27, Folder 3)
    105.4
  - Urban Land Policy-Selected Aspects of European Experience, 1969 (Box 27, Folder 4)
    106.3
  - The Greater Hartford Process, 1969 (Box 27, Folder 5)
    105.7
  - Cedar Riverside Material-J.H.K. [Jay H. Kane's file], 1970-1976 (Box 27, Folder 6)
    112.8
  - Cedar Riverside Material-J.H.K. [Jay H. Kane's file], 1970-1976 (Box 27, Folder 7)
    112.9
  - Cedar Riverside Material-J.H.K. [Jay H. Kane's file], 1970-1976 (Box 27, Folder 8)
    112.10
  - Orange County, Santa Ana and Irvine, California Development, 1971 (Box 27, Folder 9)
    112.5
  - Columbia, Maryland: A Workshop Regional Shopping Center, 1971 (Box 27, Folder 10)
    101.5
  - Cedar Riverside, 1971 (Box 27, Folder 11)
    87.1
  - Cedar Riverside, Minnesota, 1971 (Box 27, Folder 12)
    144.7
  - San Antonio Ranch, Texas, 1972 (Box 27, Folder 13)
    124.1
  - Japanese Experience, 1972 (Box 28, Folder 1)
    95.1
  - Columbia, Maryland, 1972 (Box 28, Folder 2)
    128.6
  - Citizen Participation in Columbia, 1972 (Box 28, Folder 3)
    105.3
  - Columbia, Maryland, 1972 (Box 28, Folder 4)
    128.7
  - Cedar Riverside Private Placement Memorandum [cover page only], 1973 (Box 28, Folder 5)
    113.1
  - Stockholm/Helsinki, 1973 (Box 28, Folder 6)
    94.6
  - Jonathan, 1973 (Box 28, Folder 7)
    87.4
  - Cedar Riverside New Communities Administration, 1974 (Box 28, Folder 8)
    129.5
  - Newfields-Brochure, 1974 (Box 28, Folder 9)
    116.3
  - Ganada Appraisal, 1974 (Box 28, Folder 10)
    97.7
  - St. Charles, Maryland, 1974 (Box 29, Folder 1)
    81.3
  - Cedar Riverside, 1974 (Box 29, Folder 2)
    131.3
  - Developer Cash Flow-Shenandoah, 1974 (Box 29, Folder 3)
    139.12
  - Shenandoah Analysis, 1975 (Box 29, Folder 4)
    97.2
  - Cedar-Riverside Land Company, 1975 (Box 29, Folder 5)
    100.11
  - Shenandoah-Analysis of Market Support, 1975 (Box 29, Folder 6)
    109.12
  - Developer Cash Flow-Harbison, 1975 (Box 29, Folder 7)
    138.10
  - Soul City, 1975 (Box 29, Folder 8)
    88.18
  - Park Forest South, 1976 (Box 29, Folder 9)
    87.5
  - Park Forest South, 1976 (Box 29, Folder 10)
    87.6
  - Columbia, 1976 (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - Soviet New Towns by Jack Underhill, 1976 (Box 30, Folder 1)
    106.1
  - Gananda Report Department of Housing and Urban Development Contract H4003, 1976 (Box 30, Folder 2)
    100.1
  - Developer Cash Flow-St. Charles, 1976 (Box 30, Folder 3)
    139.14
  - St. Charles, 1976 (Box 30, Folder 4)
    89.1
  - Cedar Riverside, 1976 (Box 30, Folder 5)
    131.2
  - New Communities: Problems and Potentials-A Case Study: San Antonio Ranch, 1976 (Box 30, Folder 6)
    130.5
  - New Communities: Problems and Potentials-A Case Study: Soul City, 1976 (Box 30, Folder 7)
    130.6
  - New Communities: Problems and Potentials-A Case STudy: St. Charles, 1976 (Box 30, Folder 8)
    130.7
  - Developer Cash Flow-Maumelle, 1977 (Box 30, Folder 9)
    139.9
  - Columbia, MD, 1977 (Box 30, Folder 10)
    128.5
  - Japanese Experience, 1977 (Box 31, Folder 1)
    94.7
  - Cedar Riverside Federal Appellants Response...U.S. Court of Appeals, 1977 (Box 31, Folder 2)
    109.10
  - Cedar Riverside, 1977 (Box 31, Folder 3)
    131.1
  - Cedar Riverside-U.S. District Court Summons, 1977 (Box 31, Folder 4)
    109.6
  - Fort Lincoln, 1978 (Box 31, Folder 5)
    90.2
  - Riverton, New York, 1978 (Box 31, Folder 6)
    147.1
  - Jonathan, 1978 (Box 31, Folder 7)
    87.3
  - Cedar Riverside Appellants' Reply Brief U.S. District Court of Appeals, 1979 (Box 31, Folder 8)
    109.8
  - Mercer Country Socio-Economic Impact Mitigation Assessment, 1979 (Box 31, Folder 9)
    100.09
  - Profile of Columbia Residents Living Subsidized Housing, 1979 (Box 31, Folder 10)
    112.2
  - Developer Cash Flow-Soul City, 1979 (Box 31, Folder 11)
    139.8
  - Maumelle, 1979 (Box 31, Folder 12)
    88.3
  - Geoffrey Samuels, 1979 (Box 31, Folder 13)
    483.12
    - Paper: Geoffrey Samuels, "New-Towns-In-Towns", no date; 1.
  - Shenandoah Marketing Analysis, 1979 (Box 32, Folder 1)
    116.4
  - Houston Development Choices, 1980 (Box 32, Folder 2)
    484.2
    - Letter: Lawrence O. Houstoun, Jr. to I Rocke Ransen, ca. 1980; 1.
    - Memo: John B. Clinton to Russ Marane, "Meeting with Larry Houston", April 2, 1980; 2.
  - Peachtree, Georgia, 1980s (Box 32, Folder 3)
    146.2
  - Flower Mound, Texas, 1980s (Box 32, Folder 4)
    145.1
  - Columbia, Maryland, 1980s (Box 32, Folder 5)
    144.8
  - Elk Grove, Illinois, 1980s (Box 32, Folder 6)
    144.9
  - Shenandoah Liabilities, 1980 (Box 32, Folder 7)
    98.7
  - A Summary of Fost City-A New Town in California, U.S.A, 1980 (Box 32, Folder 8)
    111.6
  - Oil Shal Regions New Town, 1980 (Box 32, Folder 9)
    100.10
  - Soviet Housing and Urban Design, 1980 (Box 32, Folder 10)
    102.4
  - Park Forest South, Illinois, 1981 (Box 32, Folder 11)
    146.1
  - St. Charles, 1981 (Box 32, Folder 12)
    88.11
  - Developer Cash Flow-Woodlands, 1981 (Box 32, Folder 13)
    139.13
  - Shenandoah, 1981 (Box 32, Folder 14)
    88.7
  - Developer Cash Flow-Flower Mound, 1982 (Box 32, Folder 15)
    139.11
  - Park Forest South, 1982 (Box 32, Folder 16)
    90.9
  - Riverton, 1982 (Box 33, Folder 1)
    88.6
  - Columbia, 1982 (Box 33, Folder 2)
    89.5
  - Woodlands, Texas Statistical Reports, Correspondence, 1973-1983 (Box 33, Folder 3)
    124.2
  - Woodlands, Texas-Underhill Notes, Summary Fact Sheets, 1983 (Box 33, Folder 4)
    124.3
  - Reston, 1983 (Box 33, Folder 5)
    91.1
  - Israeli New Towns, 1984 (Box 33, Folder 6)
    94.5
  - Woodlands, 1984-1985 (Box 33, Folder 7)
    91.4
  - Russian Pamphlets (in Russian), 1980s (Box 33, Folder 8)
    119.1
  - Census of Population and Housing, 1980s (Box 34, Folder 1)
    144.10
  - Harbison, South Carolina, 1980s (Box 34, Folder 2)
    145.2
  - Census of Poulation and Housing, 1980s (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Jonathan, Minnesota, 1980s (Box 34, Folder 4)
    145.3
  - Maumelle, Arkansas, 1980s (Box 34, Folder 5)
    145.5
  - Census of Poulation and Housing, 1980s (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - Newfields, Ohio, 1980s (Box 34, Folder 7)
    145.6
  - Census of Poulation and Housing, 1980s (Box 34, Folder 8)
  - Raddisson, New York, 1980s (Box 35, Folder 1)
    146.3
  - Census of Poulation and Housing, 1980s (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Census of Poulation and Housing, 1980s (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - Census of Poulation and Housing, 1980s (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - Census of Poulation and Housing, 1980s (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - Census of Poulation and Housing, 1980s (Box 35, Folder 7)
  - Census of Poulation and Housing, 1980s (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - Roosevelt Island, New York, 1980s (Box 36, Folder 2)
    147.2
  - Roosevelt Island, 1980s (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - St. Charles, Maryland, 1980s (Box 36, Folder 4)
    147.3
  - Census of Poulation and Housing, 1980s (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - St. Charles, Maryland, 1980s (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - Shenandoah, Georgia, 1980s (Box 37, Folder 1)
    148.1
  - Shenandoah, 1980s (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - Soul City, North Carolina, 1980s (Box 37, Folder 3)
    148.2
  - Warren County (Soul City), 1980s (Box 37, Folder 4)
  - Woodlands, Texas, 1980s (Box 37, Folder 5)
    149.3
  - Census of Poulation and Housing, 1980s (Box 37, Folder 6)
  - Census of Poulation and Housing, 1980s (Box 37, Folder 7)
  - Census of Poulation and Housing, 1980s (Box 37, Folder 8)
  - Woodlands, 1980s (Box 37, Folder 9)
  - Woodlands, 1980s (Box 37, Folder 10)
  - Woodlands and Kingwood, 1980s (Box 37, Folder 11)
  - Woodlands, 1980s (Box 37, Folder 12)
  - Census of Poulation and Housing, 1980s (Box 37, Folder 13)
  - Census of Poulation and Housing, 1980s (Box 37, Folder 14)
  - Woodlands, 1980s (Box 37, Folder 15)
  - Russian Pamphlets, 1980s (Box 38, Folder 1)
    119.2
  - Russian Booklets, 1980s (Box 38, Folder 2)
    119.3
  - Russian Booklets, 1980s (Box 38, Folder 3)
    119.4
  - Russian Booklets, 1980s (Box 38, Folder 4)
    119.5
- Series 5: Housing and Urban Development, 1970-1998; (9.5 boxes)
  Scope and Content
  This series consists of documents on welfare reform, homelessness, and housing studies in the former Union of Soviet Socialist Republics (USSR). The documents housed in this series date from 1970-1997, and the series is arranged alphabetically.
  - Articles on Homelessness: America's New Economy-Contract with America, 1995-1996 (Box 63, Folder 1)
  - Articles on Homelessness: Culhane-Frey, 1996 (Box 63, Folder 2)
  - Articles on Homelessness: Gueron-Lazere, 1991-1996 (Box 63, Folder 3)
  - Articles on Homelessness: Link-Putnam, 1991-1995 (Box 63, Folder 4)
  - Articles on Homelessness: Schill-Sherraden, 1990-1996 (Box 63, Folder 5)
  - Articles on Homelessness: Tanner-Weir, 1993-1995 (Box 63, Folder 6)
  - Community Development, 1994-1996 (Box 64, Folder 1)
  - Community Development, 1996 (Box 64, Folder 2)
  - Community Development Block Grant: Monitoring, Management Review, 1987-1997 (Box 64, Folder 3)
  - Community Development Efforts: History, Secretary's Report, 1985-1991 (Box 64, Folder 4)
  - Community Development Efforts: Urban Institute, Block Grant, 1975-1992 (Box 64, Folder 5)
  - Community Development Initiatives, 1993-1996 (Box 64, Folder 6)
  - Consolidated Plan, 1994 (Box 65, Folder 1)
  - Consolidated Plan, 1994-1995 (Box 65, Folder 2)
  - Consolidated Planning and Community Connections, 1996 (Box 65, Folder 3)
  - Consolidated Planning and Community Connections, 1996 (Box 65, Folder 4)
  - Empowerment Zones and Enterprise Communities, 1993-1994 (Box 65, Folder 5)
  - Empowerment Zones and Enterprise Communities, 1993-1996 (Box 65, Folder 6)
  - Empowerment Zones and Enterprise Communities, 1995-1997 (Box 65, Folder 7)
  - Empowerment Zones: Summary of Legislation, 1993-1996 (Box 66, Folder 1)
  - Empowerment Zones: Table of Contents; July 27 Testimony, 1989-1994 (Box 66, Folder 2)
  - Enterprise Zone Briefing Materials, 1989-1990 (Box 66, Folder 3)
  - Enterprise Zone Documents: Office of Program Analysis and Evaluation, 1985-1988 (Box 66, Folder 4)
  - Enterprise Zone Documents: Office of Program Analysis and Evaluation, 1985-1988 (Box 66, Folder 5)
  - Housing and Urban Development: Environment and Memos, 1997 (Box 66, Folder 6)
  - Fair Housing Action and Performance, 1990s (Box 66, Folder 7)
  - Fair Housing History: Lending and Solutions, 1990s (Box 67, Folder 1)
  - Federal Register, 1993-1994 (Box 67, Folder 2)
  - General Accounting Office (GAO), 1989-1996 (Box 67, Folder 3)
  - General Accounting Office (GAO), 1989-1996 (Box 67, Folder 4)